wsdeal.com 2008-09-12

# Privacy Policy_WholeSale Earphones Electronics Direct From China!

**Privacy Policy** ** **

WSDeal.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We promise to keep all the personally 

identifiable information that you share with us confidential. We only collect personal 

information from wholesalers in order to process orders, and provide a personal and 

customized shopping experience. Please review our privacy policy for more detail.

**Collection Of Information**

When you visit our website, we do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. For instance, we do require registration when you want to order. If you decide to order, or if you request other information from us, you will be asked to provide certain information and details, including your Email, Name, Street Address, Post Code, City, Country, Telephone Number.

**Use Of Information**

We may use the information you provide to respond to your requests for additional information, to contact you, if necessary, to service your account or for other administrative purposes. We may also access your information to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems, to enforce agreements between us, or for marketing purposes. In addition, for certain transactions, our system may use your transaction details to automate and to streamline your transaction by checking for electronic data compliance, providing reporting features, and transferring data from previous forms to those of the current transaction. 

We may also use the information you provide for certain mailing initiatives. For example, you may sometimes receive an invitation to answer surveys or try out new products and services from WSDeal.com. Your feedback helps us develop new products and services based on your needs. 

You always have a choice about receiving mailings, surveys or information about products and services from us. Each e-mail you receive has an "Unsubscribe" option. As a registered member, you can also advise us which types of e-mail you wish to receive by updating your Notifications page. 

**Updating Personal Information** ****

If the personal information WSDeal.com has gathered from you changes or you no longer desire our service, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any personal data you have previously provided to us.You can change it yourself in customer centern or [contact us](http://www.wsdeal.com/contact.asp).

**Notice Of Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. However, if any changes do occur, we will publish the changes to our web site and post a notice on the home page that a new privacy policy has been implemented. We will also take reasonable steps to contact you personally to let you know of the new changes. Should the company be bought or sold to someone else, we will take reasonable steps to notify you personally. You will then be given the option to keep your account open or to terminate. 

**Fraudulent Charge Protection** ****

If a third party obtains your personal information from a purchase made with WSDeal.com and uses that information to perpetrate credit card fraud, you are protected. 

So we can just send order to the [paypal](http://www.paypal.com/) address(not info address) if you want to pay by [paypal](http://www.paypal.com/). If the [paypal](http://www.paypal.com/) address is not right,please change it before you pay.

**Legal Disclaimer** ****

The only time WSDeal.com will disclose personal information is when required to by law or with the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the law. 

If you have questions about this privacy statement, please [contact us](http://www.wsdeal.com/contact.asp).
